<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>HANN Planet</title>
  
  
  <link href="http://example.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://example.com/"/>
  <updated>2021-12-23T10:35:17.476Z</updated>
  <id>http://example.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>HANN</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>HANN&#39;s Daily Life</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/12/18/private/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/12/18/private/</id>
    <published>2021-12-19T02:13:55.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-12-23T10:35:17.476Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="volunteer">Volunteer<a title="#volunteer" href="#volunteer"></a></h2><p>I love participating in voluntary work in my spare life. I volunteered in professional events like China-CEEC Arts Cooperation Forum and daily events like Mayday “Just Rock It,” Bird’s Nest Concert, and Earth Day Festival. I enjoy my time most when I’m accompanying the elderly and children. It’s an honor to help the world in return.</p><p><img src="images/private/v1.jpg" alt="volunteer1" loading="lazy"><br>Hospital Guidance Volunteer in Beijing | 2015</p><p><img src="images/private/v2.jpg" alt="volunteer2" loading="lazy"><br>Accompany Autistic children | 2016</p><p><img src="images/private/v3.jpg" alt="volunteer3" loading="lazy"><br>Accompany the elderly with Alzheimer’s disease | 2016</p><p><img src="images/private/sb1.jpg" alt="volunteer4" loading="lazy"><br>Santa Barbara Earth Day Festival | 2017</p><p><img src="images/private/heart.jpg" alt="volunteer5" loading="lazy"><br>American Heart Association Heart Saver Volunteer | 2019</p><hr><h2 id="debate">Debate<a title="#debate" href="#debate"></a></h2><p>I joined the English debate team back in high school. I enjoyed cooperating with others and considering social issues rationally and statistically.<br><img src="images/private/deb1.jpg" alt="debate" loading="lazy"><br>National Speech and Debate Association（NSDA in China) | 2014</p><p>I joined the university’s Chinese debate team after college (since there was no English debate team back then). I was so lucky to make many friends by preparing for the debate competition and meeting them during the debate. Some of us became best friends even till now. Though friendship always comes first, it’s glad to know we also won a lot of awards at the same time.<br><img src="images/private/deb2.jpg" alt="debate2" loading="lazy"></p><hr><h2 id="dance-&amp;-sing">Dance &amp; Sing<a title="#dance-&amp;-sing" href="#dance-&amp;-sing"></a></h2><p>I have been learning Chinese classical dance and modern dance since 6-year-old. Later, I fell in love with KPOP. While learning dance by myself, I also recorded and posted dance tutorial videos online.<br><img src="images/private/dance1.jpg" alt="dance" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/private/dance2.jpg" alt="dance2" loading="lazy"></p><hr><h2 id="photography">Photography<a title="#photography" href="#photography"></a></h2><p>I took professional photography courses during my undergraduate studies. Planning and shooting media news, micro-film or documentary is also part of my daily life. I truly enjoyed recording the world around me using my camera. My affection for video can be also seen from my love for dramas on streaming apps (like Disney+ and Netflix). I hope one day I can work in my dream companies.<br><img src="images/private/hh1.jpg" alt="photography2" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/private/hh2.jpg" alt="photography3" loading="lazy"><br>Landscape Photography | 2016</p><p><img src="images/private/HC02.jpg" alt="photography2" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/private/HC03.jpg" alt="photography3" loading="lazy"><br>Portrait Photography | 2017</p><p><img src="images/private/photo.jpg" alt="photography" loading="lazy"><br>Hann as the Live TV Host | 2018</p><hr><h2 id="instrument">Instrument<a title="#instrument" href="#instrument"></a></h2><p>I began learning the piano when 6-year-old. I recently developed an interest in Ukulele and guitar, and I can now sing and play together.<br><img src="images/private/piano.jpg" alt="piano1" loading="lazy"><br>(You can watch some of my covers on my YouTube channel:<br><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1K2eeRRaY4I">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1K2eeRRaY4I</a>)</p><p><em>Nice to Meet You</em></p><hr>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;volunteer&quot;&gt;Volunteer&lt;a title=&quot;#volunteer&quot; href=&quot;#volunteer&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love participating in voluntary work in my spare life. I </summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="HANN" scheme="http://example.com/tags/HANN/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Biography of HANN</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/12/10/aboutme/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/12/10/aboutme/</id>
    <published>2021-12-10T06:13:55.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-12-23T09:28:55.381Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>HANN - A Marketing Researcher with Data Analysis background and interests in Television Industry.</p><p>Han combines academic training in television with professional experience in the media industry to launch a future career in entertainment management.<br>Han received a bachelor’s degree from the Communication University of China, majoring in broadcast television. She acquired solid academic knowledge through courses like TV Program Planning, News Theory, and Communication Research Methods during her undergraduate studies.<br><img src="images/aboutme/cuc.jpg" alt="CUC" loading="lazy"></p><p>She also studied at the University of California, Santa Barbara, as a communication and media exchange student during her Sophomore year.<br><img src="images/aboutme/sb.jpg" alt="Santa Barbara" loading="lazy"></p><p>In 2019, Han joined Sony Pictures Television in Beijing as a development intern. She engaged in the China-Russia cooperated TV project Chosen II, contributed to the screenwriting and Chinese-English translation; helped it reach 629,000 online views. She analyzed several ongoing and upcoming TV projects and conducted research on trending topics, including PTSD, the Esports industry, and young adults’ attitudes towards love.<br><img src="images/aboutme/sony.jpg" alt="Sony" loading="lazy"></p><p>Earlier, Han was a business development intern at Tencent Technology Enterprise (Beijing). She took charge of the Internet celebrity business development for the QQ Kandian platform, reaching more than 1,000 influencers from TikTok, Kwai, and Weibo. She collaborated on several top business projects, independently hosting 16 up-to-date discussions and inspiring celebrities to create more than 1,300 original social media posts.<br>Han also worked as a freelance promotion planner to help companies including RED, Youku, and FaceU successfully publicize media products and television shows.<br><img src="images/aboutme/cuc2.jpg" alt="CUC" loading="lazy"></p><p>Han is currently pursuing a master’s degree in marketing communication research at Boston University. Besides rich knowledge in marketing communication, she is still pursuing a certificate in data analysis from the Computer Science Department. Understanding coding rules then applying them to real-world problems could be challenging. Still, she successfully learned methods like implementing regression models to investigate complicated social issues like mental health. She is also qualified to measure how much one aspect like alcohol or family heredity affects depression and then evades it through strategic recognition.<br>When chasing academia, she is also concerned about the unpredictable market in authentic situations. During her work as a marketing internship in Bilibili technology company, she analyzed influencers’ content on Bilibili, managed and supervised the quality, time, and cost of projects. She also developed outstanding skills in communication with influencers and clients, who comes from Gaming (Honor of Kings, Fantasy Westward Journey), Cosmetics (Elizabeth Arden, La Mer, and Innisfree) to Technology (Dell, Intel, and MAO KING).<br><img src="images/aboutme/b3.jpg" alt="Han in Bilibili" loading="lazy"><br>(Han starred in Bilibili 2021 social recruitment promotion video, full video:<a href="https://www.bilibili.com/video/BV1cT4y1Z79K?spm_id_from=333.999.0.0">https://www.bilibili.com/video/BV1cT4y1Z79K?spm_id_from=333.999.0.0</a>)</p><p>Now, Han is looking forward to a future path in both academia and industry.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;HANN - A Marketing Researcher with Data Analysis background and interests in Television Industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Han combines academic training i</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="HANN" scheme="http://example.com/tags/HANN/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Analysis on Life Expectancy (Data Visulization with R)</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/11/28/life/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/11/28/life/</id>
    <published>2021-11-28T16:21:47.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-12-23T10:21:24.953Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="dataset-details">Dataset Details<a title="#dataset-details" href="#dataset-details"></a></h2><p>This data is from WHO and United Nations website collected with the help of Deeksha Russell and Duan Wang. Detailed Resources are on: <a href="https://www.kaggle.com/kumarajarshi/life-expectancy-who">https://www.kaggle.com/kumarajarshi/life-expectancy-who</a></p><p>The dataset consists of 22 Columns and 2938 rows which meant 20 predicting variables. All predicting variables was then divided into several broad categories: Immunization related factors, Mortality factors, Economical factors and Social factors.</p><hr><h2 id="objectives">Objectives<a title="#objectives" href="#objectives"></a></h2><p>1.General Information about Life Expectancy Distribution<br>1.1 Detailed information about life expectancy according to countries<br>1.2 Life expectancy distribution<br>1.3 Boxplot about Life Expectancy by Country<br>1.4 Central Limited Theorem<br>1.5 Sampling methods<br>2.What factors really affect the Life expectancy?<br>3.Among them, which influence life expectancy most? How much?<br>4.What is the impact of schooling on life expectancy?<br>5.What’s the relationship between Infant and Adult Mortality &amp; Life Expectancy?<br>6.What’s the relationship between HIV/AIDS and life expectancy?<br>7.What’s the relationship between years and life expectancy?</p><hr><h2 id="notice">Notice<a title="#notice" href="#notice"></a></h2><p>Due to the RMarkdown format issue, the result can not be uploaded<br>online. Following are the screenshots of my findings:</p><hr><p><img src="images/life/1.jpg" alt="life" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/2.jpg" alt="life2" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/3.jpg" alt="life3" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/4.jpg" alt="life4" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/5.jpg" alt="life5" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/6.jpg" alt="life6" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/7.jpg" alt="life7" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/8.jpg" alt="life8" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/9.jpg" alt="life9" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/10.jpg" alt="life10" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/11.jpg" alt="life11" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/12.jpg" alt="life12" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/13.jpg" alt="life13" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/14.jpg" alt="life14" loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/life/15.jpg" alt="life15" loading="lazy"></p><hr><h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion<a title="#conclusion" href="#conclusion"></a></h2><p>Due to the concern for human health, I chose this topic to testify that how much an unhealthy daily lifestyle would affect people’s life expectancy. After calculation, I discovered that people with higher BMI, a country with a lower mortality rate, tend to have a high life expectancy. What’s more, income and schooling also strongly correlate with life expectancy.<br>I also found that government expenditure and GDP don’t strongly correlate with life expectancy. I primarily considered alcohol a trigger to a shorter life, but the result converted my thoughts. I would love to suggest countries focus more on increasing the overall income of their residents rather than weigh too much on government expenditure and GDP.<br>There are still many flaws and shortcomings in this survey. The overall statistics pool is narrow, more samples can help dig deeper into this topic.<br>In a nutshell, I hope these findings would be helpful in some ways.</p><hr>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;dataset-details&quot;&gt;Dataset Details&lt;a title=&quot;#dataset-details&quot; href=&quot;#dataset-details&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This data is from WHO and United Na</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="Research" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Research/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Conventional Report on Disney+</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/11/25/disney/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/11/25/disney/</id>
    <published>2021-11-25T17:55:54.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-12-23T10:22:58.897Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="objective">Objective<a title="#objective" href="#objective"></a></h2><p>Find out what drive young adults (18-24) to subscribe Disney+, and how to improve Disney+ service (content &amp; interface).</p><hr><h2 id="methodology">Methodology<a title="#methodology" href="#methodology"></a></h2><ol><li>Desk Research</li><li>Focus Group (6-8 people)</li><li>One to One Interview</li><li>Video Ethnography</li><li>Social Media Listening</li></ol><hr><p><img src="images/disney/info.png" alt loading="lazy"><br>This is an infographic compares Disney+ with Netflix.</p><p>Follows are the detailed report of Disney+.</p><p><img src="images/disney/cr1.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr2.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr3.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr4.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr5.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr6.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr7.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr8.png" alt loading="lazy"><br>(To watch this, click: <a href="https://youtu.be/zOtTdMMKkXA">https://youtu.be/zOtTdMMKkXA</a>)</p><p><img src="images/disney/cr9.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr10.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr11.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr12.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr13.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr14.png" alt loading="lazy"><br>(To watch this, click: <a href="https://youtu.be/EEwiyD31rZo">https://youtu.be/EEwiyD31rZo</a>)</p><p><img src="images/disney/cr15.png" alt loading="lazy"><br>(To watch the full video ethnography, click: <a href="https://youtu.be/QFzuzsa-UDk">https://youtu.be/QFzuzsa-UDk</a>)</p><p><img src="images/disney/cr16.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr17.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr18.png" alt loading="lazy"><br>(To watch this, click: <a href="https://youtu.be/tf4IuaPn18g">https://youtu.be/tf4IuaPn18g</a>)</p><p><img src="images/disney/cr19.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr20.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr21.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr22.png" alt loading="lazy"><br>(To watch recommended function of Bilibili, click: <a href="https://youtu.be/MFAb0cROkZo">https://youtu.be/MFAb0cROkZo</a>)</p><p>(To watch discussion on ideal streaming apps, click: <a href="https://youtu.be/VHrLJxeY-88">https://youtu.be/VHrLJxeY-88</a>)</p><p><img src="images/disney/cr23.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr24.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr25.png" alt loading="lazy"><br><img src="images/disney/cr26.png" alt loading="lazy"></p><p>*All rights reserved.</p><hr>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;objective&quot;&gt;Objective&lt;a title=&quot;#objective&quot; href=&quot;#objective&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Find out what drive young adults (18-24) to subscribe Disne</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="disney+" scheme="http://example.com/tags/disney/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Learn from Kpop Female Groups</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/04/11/kpopgroup/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/04/11/kpopgroup/</id>
    <published>2021-04-11T07:50:32.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-12-23T06:18:33.670Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="brave-girls-be-brave">Brave Girls-Be Brave<a title="#brave-girls-be-brave" href="#brave-girls-be-brave"></a></h2><p>I was shocked when I woke up on March 4 and saw “Rollin” trending on the top sector of Weibo. When I clicked the hashtag, a video popped up. I couldn’t believe it was exactly the song I listened to almost four years ago. As a 13-year Kpop lover, I always follow the latest music trends and check every week’s latest performance stages. Hundreds of groups debuted in South Korea every year, and numerous songs came out, but most of them only went nameless. The song “Rollin” was one of those unknown songs.<br><img src="images/bg1.jpg" alt="Brave Girls Orignal Concept is " loading="lazy"><br>(The original concept of “Rollin” is Sexy)</p><p>A YouTuber named “비디터ᴠɪᴅɪᴛᴏʀ” edited Brave Girls’ live stages and combined it with interactive comments under those performance videos. He of she uploaded it on February 24. (See more on: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cfHWIqJkEf4">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cfHWIqJkEf4</a>)<br>A few days later, more and more people gathered. Most of them have served in South Korea’s army before.<br>Thousands of South Korean soldiers loved this song mainly because of Brave Girls’ endless effort and their passion for the stage.<br><img src="images/bg3.jpg" alt="A Screenshot of the Popular Video" loading="lazy"></p><p>Performing in the military is an energy-consuming job with little salary but long-time travel. Most of the famous female groups only attended no more than three shows. However, BraveGirls attended almost all of them. Their longest journey took 12 hours, and the payback was less than $80. Despite the difficulties, every time, Brave Girls smiled and enjoyed the performance “as if it’s the last.”<br>For example, to perform the song “Rollin”, everyone should dance on a chair. One time, the group member Yuna fell from the chair during the performance. She quickly got up and stood on the chair again, perfectly finishing the song.<br><img src="images/bg2.jpg" alt="Live Performance" loading="lazy"><br>(During the performance, BraveGirls need to dance on the chair.)</p><p>All of a sudden, a miracle happened.<br>Until March 24 24.00 pm (Korean Time), this song has achieved the “perfect all-kill” 244 times, ranking fourth on South Korea’s all-time history music chart. Also, I have to admit it’s the most harmonious time in the last decade of Kpop fan clubs: Everyone supported BraveGirls’ return and cheered for their success.<br>It’s unbelievable in Kpop history.<br>Brave Girls did it.</p><p>The most significant factor to their late success is always their love for the stage and their braveness.<br>They persisted and never gave up.<br><img src="images/bg4.jpg" alt="BraveGirls on 2021 MMA" loading="lazy"><br>So have you heard any of Brave Girls’ songs? Which one is your favorite?</p><hr><h2 id="dreamcatcher--be-what-you-wanna-be">Dreamcatcher -Be what you wanna be<a title="#dreamcatcher--be-what-you-wanna-be" href="#dreamcatcher--be-what-you-wanna-be"></a></h2><p>I became fascinated with Dreamcatcher’s concept since its debut. As the first and ever Kpop female rock group, I knew from the beginning that Dreamcatcher was destined to a tough road.<br>Formerly known as Minx, the five-member girl group debuted in 2014. They followed the significant trends, sang sweet love songs, and were just a flash in the pan. In 2017, with two new members, the group re-debut under the name Dreamcatcher.<br><img src="images/dc1.jpg" alt="Orignal concept of Minx" loading="lazy"><br>(Original concept of Minx is Cute)</p><p>I didn’t notice the group Minx before, but the fresh style of Dreamcatcher immediately caught my attention. This time, they abandoned the popular trend: Girl crush or sweet melody, they stuck to the rock-band style pop song with the concept of “Nightmare.” Their songs are unique in Kpop history since no one did before, and it’s nearly a rebellion against the traditional aesthetic standard for Kpop female groups.<br><img src="images/dc4.jpg" alt loading="lazy"></p><p>Traditional beliefs like “Female groups should be sweet” or “It’s weird for female groups to perform rock songs on stage” even confused some of the members initially. I remember the main vocal, Siyeon, once talked about her anxiety after deciding the concept: “Though I love singing rock songs, is this the right path?”<br><img src="images/dc2.jpg" alt="Chase Me" loading="lazy"><br>(Dreamcatcher’s debut song: Chase Me. You can watch the official video on: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zihoyz0u_cs">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zihoyz0u_cs</a>)</p><p>Surprisingly, Dreamcatcher’s songs went popular in South America and Europe. For example, after releasing their second album and their first EP “Prequel,” the album debuted at No. 5 on the Billboard World Albums Chart and peaked at No. 1 on the US iTunes K-Pop Top 100 Chart.<br>Dreamcatcher’s album sales have reached more than 100.000, and they have toured more than 20 countries. Though they haven’t won the first prize in South Korea’s music shows, I believe more and more people will discover their uniqueness and support them as long as they stick to who they want to become.<br>“We are Insomnia; we don’t sleep on talents.”<br><img src="images/dc3.jpg" alt="Whole Group" loading="lazy"></p><p>Do you love listening to rock songs in your spare time? Have you “tried” Dreamcatcher’s songs before?</p><hr><h2 id="girls'-generation--never-stop-chasing-for-the-perfect">Girls’ Generation- Never stop chasing for the perfect<a title="#girls'-generation--never-stop-chasing-for-the-perfect" href="#girls'-generation--never-stop-chasing-for-the-perfect"></a></h2><p>I am a Kpop lover. To be specific, I am a superfan of Kpop female groups.<br>I searched for “which celebrity has the same birthday with you” when I found “Taeyeon,” the group leader of Girls’ Generation. That’s the beginning and the reason why I began to know Kpop.<br><img src="images/gg1.jpg" alt="GG" loading="lazy"><br>(Girls’ Generation debuted on August 5, 2017)</p><p>Expressing your love for female groups sometimes creates confusion and misunderstanding. People asked me: You are a girl. Why do you love female idols? I was offended when I was young, but now I realize that I shouldn’t be embarrassed about what I love. So I told them I support female Kpop groups because I cherish the braveness, talents, and endless effort they devote to become perfect in their career.<br><img src="images/gg4.jpg" alt="GG2" loading="lazy"></p><p>An important factor about South Korea’s Kpop culture is their trainee culture. To become a qualified idol, teenagers have to practice three to four years, and some trainees like Sunny from Girls’ Generation may even need to practice seven years to stand on the stage finally. Meanwhile, females always have to work harder to stand out among their peers, and it’s more difficult for them to debut in the ferocious entertainment industry successfully.<br>At the same time, few female groups could stand the test of time. Compared with male groups who have to finish the mandatory military service in South Korea, only a few female groups could last longer than seven years.<br>That’s why someone said Girls’ Generation “extended the average ‘lifetime’ of Kpop female groups.”<br><img src="images/gg3.jpg" alt="GG3" loading="lazy"></p><p>Girls’ Generation has debuted 14 years, and the group is known for being one of the prominent South Korean figures and one of the most popular Kpop groups worldwide. It has earned numerous accolades and the honorific nickname “The Nation’s Girl Group” in South Korea.<br>Currently, every member is dedicated to a specific area they love, like singing, hosting, acting, musical, and cooking. They proved that females could do everything as long as they sought the opportunity and stuck to their purpose.<br>The group’s central dancer, Hyoyeon, once talked about her group members on a show: “In fact, every one of us has different characteristics, and sometimes conflicts occur. However, as a group, we have the same purpose, and that’s what unites us.” Another member Sooyoung also agreed; she talked about what inspired her has always been “the spirit of Girls’ Generation.”<br><img src="images/gg2.jpg" alt="GG4" loading="lazy"></p><p>So what’s the spirit of the Girls’ Generation?<br>Never stop chasing for the perfect.</p><p>Do you know other female groups’ spirits? Feel free to share yours under the comment box below.</p><p>[This passage was initially written on March 25th, 2021, for course CM707; the recent edit is on April 11th.]</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <summary type="html">As a 14 years fan of Kpop female group, what have I learnt from these girls?</summary>
    
    
    
    
    <category term="Kpop" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Kpop/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>One-to-One Interview with Actress Xin Zhang</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/04/09/qa/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/04/09/qa/</id>
    <published>2021-04-09T08:30:37.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-12-23T10:09:34.297Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Original Title: The Life of a “Middle Line” Actress</p><p>Xin Zhang is a 25-year-old Chinese actress and singer. She graduated from the Beijing Film Academy, debuted in 2016 and became an actress till now. She has acted in television dramas like “Arsenal Military Academy”, &quot;The Legends” and “Detective”.<br><img src="images/kim/09.jpg" alt loading="lazy"></p><p><em>Q: It’s been a while since our last conversation. How’s your going recently?</em></p><p>I just finished shooting one TV series called: “Snow Lover” and went back home to take some rest. I acted as the supporting actress in this opera and my character was a “nobody” actress named Lin Jinjin, quite similar to my current situation.</p><p><em>Yeah, but you got 2 million followers on Weibo which seems far more than “nobody”, right?</em></p><p>You can say that, if you see from this perspective. Personally, I would view myself as those who are in the middle line: not so famous but also not that anonymous. Sometimes my schedule would be really busy and sometimes I could be unemployed for more than six months. It’s also another factor that triggered my anxiety last year since all my work was shut down due to the pandemic.</p><p><em>I got it. So what’s your original plan if the pandemic didn’t occur?</em></p><p>The ski-set TV drama “Snow Lover” was supposed to be shot in the winter vacation of 2020. However, due to the pandemic, the snow had already melted by the time I could go out, so it was postponed. Later, I planned to act in a modern TV drama in September while the skiing drama suddenly notified me that it would start shooting in November. So the two dramas bumped their schedules, and I had to give up the latter. Sadly, the “Snow Lover” didn’t start filming until last December and I was so anxious during the waiting. You know, actors are not like other jobs which you can do freelance work while you are unemployed. In such circumstances, we can do nothing but wait.<br><img src="images/kim/10.jpg" alt loading="lazy"></p><p><em>Yes, acting is not as adjustable as other occupations. I noticed that you had covered a lot of songs on Tiktok during those days. I assumed that singing could help you relieve yourself, right?</em></p><p>Yes, of course. Music is like my secret weapon. When I am singing, I can focus on my lyrics and my feelings. I won’t be bothered by anything else, it helps clear my mind. I always bring the guitar with me even though I have a shooting schedule: piano and guitar are my friends, they could help me compose and accompany me forever.<br><img src="images/kim/11.jpg" alt loading="lazy"></p><p><em>I have also played the piano since childhood, I understand such feelings. You also wrote the song “UR” for the drama “Detective” which sounds so beautiful to me. The drama “Detective” is also your first time acting as the leading role, do you have some special experiences or memories to share with me?</em></p><p>Thank you for your support. Most of the time, I talk about other actors and actresses during interviews, like what I have learnt from them and how we helped each other. In fact, the person who influenced me most is the styling designer assistant. I could tell she was younger than me from her appearance. Everyday she helped me with my styling during the shooting. For example, if my hair was messed up by the wind or my clothes were uneven, she would immediately fix it for me. On the wrap day, after my last scene, she asked me if she could have a picture with me and I said yes. When we stood together and began to take pictures, she suddenly noticed that my hair was a bit messy and she quickly helped me fix it even though I didn’t have any shooting schedule later. She loved her job so much and I was touched by her subconscious behavior. I wish she could have a brilliant future.<br><img src="images/kim/14.jpg" alt loading="lazy"></p><p><em>I’m sure she will. So how does it feel when you could act as the leading role in one drama for the first time in your life?</em></p><p>I was a bit worried at first but I became ambitious about it. Acting as the leading role means your character would be more “deep” and “solid” since the playwright would focus more on your role. The role would have more lines and the actor could have more “belief” in their characters. I mean, take my last character Lin Jinjin for example, sometimes I don’t see the reason why she behaved like this. I was shooting in a scene of Lin quarreling with her boyfriend on the day you paid a visit. I  was confused about the reason why the two characters suddenly reunited. What’s more, there were so many kissing scenes which seemed quite inappropriate for me. I mean, I don’t mind having kissing scenes during the shooting, but kissing after saying one sentence was so strange and that made it hard for me to immerse in the character.<br><img src="images/kim/02.jpg" alt loading="lazy"></p><p><em>Right, I remembered you look really tired that day but the audience may not know because they will only see actors dressed elegantly and starring on the screen.<br>Nowadays, many teenagers want to become stars or show up on TV. Do you have any recommendations or advice for them?</em></p><p>Personally, I would say being an actress is an ordinary occupation just like others. The main difference may be we appear on the screen more often than others but it doesn’t mean it’s a simple job with no sweat. I welcome anyone who has acting dreams but you may need to think deeper before stepping into this industry.<br><img src="images/kim/12.jpg" alt loading="lazy"></p><p><em>Thank you so much for your time!</em></p><hr>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Original Title: The Life of a “Middle Line” Actress&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xin Zhang is a 25-year-old Chinese actress and singer. She graduated from the </summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="interview" scheme="http://example.com/tags/interview/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
