<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>HANN Planet</title>
  
  
  <link href="http://example.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://example.com/"/>
  <updated>2021-12-14T00:02:37.325Z</updated>
  <id>http://example.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>HANN</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>About Me</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/12/13/hello-world/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/12/13/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2021-12-13T21:05:41.931Z</published>
    <updated>2021-12-14T00:02:37.325Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A Marketing Researcher with Data Analysis background and interests in Television Industry.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A Marketing Researcher with Data Analysis background and interests in Television Industry.&lt;/p&gt;
</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Consumer Insight</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/11/03/consumer/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/11/03/consumer/</id>
    <published>2021-11-03T21:03:50.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-12-14T01:06:43.205Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Investigation on Chinese Consumer Insights</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Investigation on Chinese Consumer Insights&lt;/p&gt;
</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="HANN" scheme="http://example.com/tags/HANN/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Life Expectancy</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/10/30/My-New-Post/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/10/30/My-New-Post/</id>
    <published>2021-10-30T22:31:34.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-12-14T00:02:35.243Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is a data analysis report on Life Expectancy based on …</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is a data analysis report on Life Expectancy based on …&lt;/p&gt;
</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="life expectancy" scheme="http://example.com/tags/life-expectancy/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Learn from Kpop Female Groups</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/04/11/kpopgroup/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/04/11/kpopgroup/</id>
    <published>2021-04-11T07:50:32.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-12-14T08:01:42.543Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>#1. Brave Girls-Be Brave<br>I was shocked when I woke up on March 4 and saw “Rollin” trending on the top sector of Weibo. When I clicked the hashtag, a video popped up. I couldn’t believe it was exactly the song I listened to almost four years ago. As a 13-year Kpop lover, I always follow the latest music trends and check every week’s latest performance stages. Hundreds of groups debuted in South Korea every year, and numerous songs came out, but most of them only went nameless. The song “Rollin” was one of those unknown songs.<br><img src="/.com//bg1.jpg" alt="bg1" loading="lazy"><br>(The original concept of “Rollin” is Sexy)</p><p>A YouTuber named “비디터ᴠɪᴅɪᴛᴏʀ” edited Brave Girls’ live stages and combined it with interactive comments under those performance videos. He of she uploaded it on February 24. A few days later, more and more people gathered. Most of them have served in South Korea’s army before.<br>Thousands of South Korean soldiers loved this song mainly because of Brave Girls’ endless effort and their passion for the stage.<br>Performing in the military is an energy-consuming job with little salary but long-time travel. Most of the famous female groups only attended no more than three shows. However, BraveGirls attended almost all of them. Their longest journey took 12 hours, and the payback was less than $80. Despite the difficulties, every time, Brave Girls smiled and enjoyed the performance “as if it’s the last.”<br>For example, to perform the song “Rollin”, everyone should dance on a chair. One time, the group member Yuna fell from the chair during the performance. She quickly got up and stood on the chair again, perfectly finishing the song.<br><img src="/.com//bg2.jpg" alt="bg2" loading="lazy"></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;#1. Brave Girls-Be Brave&lt;br&gt;
I was shocked when I woke up on March 4 and saw “Rollin” trending on the top sector of Weibo. When I clicked</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="Kpop" scheme="http://example.com/tags/Kpop/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
